<resources>
    <string-array name="sections">
        <item name="generator">Gerador</item>
        <item name="names">Nomes</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="save">Salvar</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancelar</string>
    <string name="generator_empty_state">Deslize para baixo para gerar nomes</string>
    <string name="invalid_syllable_character">Sílabas somente podem conter caracteres alfabeticos, sem acentos e minusculos</string>
    <string name="invalid_syllable_length">Sílabas devem ter pelo menos dois caracteres</string>
    <string name="invalid_syllable_vowel">Sílabas devem conter pelo menos uma vogal</string>
    <string name="invalid_pattern_no_braces">Deve conter pelo menos um padrão dentro de chaves {}</string>
    <string name="invalid_pattern_uneven_braces">Deve conter a mesma quantidade de chaves abertas { e fechadas }</string>
    <string name="invalid_pattern_start">Padrão precisa iniciar com um destes caracteres: : X/x (qualquer um), C/c (consoante), V/v (vogal)</string>
    <string name="invalid_pattern_length">Tamanho do padrão precisa ser pelo menos 1 e no máximo 9</string>
    <string name="invalid_pattern_range">Intervalo do padrão precisa ser pelo menos 1-1 e no máximo 9-9</string>
    <string name="confirm_delete_syllable">Excluir sílaba?</string>
    <string name="confirm_delete_pattern">Excluir padrão?</string>
    <string name="confirm_delete_name">Excluir nome?</string>
    <string name="delete">Excluir</string>
    <string name="title_save_pattern">Salvar padrão</string>
    <string name="title_save_syllable">Salvar sílaba</string>
    <string name="title_save_name">Salvar nome</string>
    <string name="title_info">Info</string>
    <string name="generator_info_no_syllables">Você não tem nenhuma sílaba ativa. Por favor, ative ou crie alguma.</string>
    <string name="generator_info_no_patterns">Você não tem nenhum padrão ativo. Por favor, ative ou crie algum.</string>
    <string name="generator_info_no_consonant_syllables">Você possui apenas padrões ativos que requerem consoantes, mas nenhuma sílaba ativa que inicia com alguma.</string>
    <string name="generator_info_no_vowel_syllables">Você possui apenas padrões ativos que requerem vogais, mas nenhuma sílaba ativa que inicia com alguma.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_used_libraries">Bibliotecas usadas</string>
    <string name="preference_about_app">Sobre o app</string>
    <string name="preference_patterns">Padrões</string>
    <string name="preference_syllables">Sílabas</string>
    <string name="preference_about_app_used_libraries_summary">As bibliotecas Android que usei para deixar esse app tão chique.</string>
    <string name="preference_patterns_summary">Edite os padrões usados para geração dos nomes.</string>
    <string name="preference_syllables_summary">Edite as sílabas usadas para geração dos nomes.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Preferências</string>
    <string name="title_activity_patterns">Padrões</string>
    <string name="title_activity_syllables">Sílabas</string>
    <string name="generated_names_amount_selector">Gerar %s</string>
    <string name="preference_feedback">Send feedback (english only)</string>
    <string name="preference_feedback_url">https://goo.gl/forms/BmL7Zh64fiJOjwNa2</string>
    <string name="preference_feedback_summary">Opens in your browser</string>
    <!-- Please translate into portuguese -->
    <string name="preference_helper_summary">He translated the app into portuguese and has some cool projects too! Have a look: https://github.com/adrielcafe</string>
    <string name="preference_patterns_tutorial">Tutorial</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tutorial">Tutorial</string>
    <string name="tutorial_main">
        To add a new name, syllable or pattern just click on the \"+\" button in the bottom right
        corner of the lists.\n\n

        To show the edit and delete buttons of a name, syllable or pattern simply swipe from right
        to left on the desired entry. This will hide the \"+\" button, so to show it again swipe
        from left to right on the entry.
    </string>
    <string name="tutorial_patterns">
        Patterns can contain fixed items but must always contain at least one syllable-part.\n\n
        A syllable-part has to start with a \"{\" and end with a \"}\".\n\n
        The first character of it must be either \"X\", \"C\" or \"V\". This determines if the
        first syllable should start with a consonant (C), a vowel (V) or if it can be random (X).
        Setting this character to lowercase or uppercase also sets the first character of the
        starting syllable to lowercase or uppercase.\n\n
        Then follows the amount of used syllables. Either set a fixed number between \"1\" and \"9\"
        or set a range between \"1-1\" to \"9-9\".\n\n
        Outside of these syllable parts, you can add anything you like and it will be added to the
        generated parts.\n\n\n\n

        To understand the previous text a bit better, I will explain what the patterns provided
        at installation will do.\n\n

        \"{X2-9}\" will generate names starting with an uppercase random syllable and these names
        will contain between 2 and 9 syllables.\n\n

        \"{V1} {C1}\'{c1-4}\" will generate names starting with one uppercase syllable that has a
        vowel as first character.\n
        Then follows a static blank space.\n
        Then one uppercase syllable that starts with a consonant will follow, directly followed by
        a static apostrophe.\n
        The last syllable-part will add a lowercase consonant syllable and will contain between 1
        and 4 syllables in total.
    </string>
    <string name="info_names">
        To add a new name just click on the \"+\" button in the bottom right corner.\n\n
        To show the edit and delete buttons of a name swipe from right to left on the entry. This
        will hide the \"+\" button, so to show it again swipe from left to right on the entry
    </string>
    <string name="info_syllables">
        To add a new syllable just click on the \"+\" button in the bottom right corner.\n\n
        To show the edit and delete buttons of a syllable swipe from right to left on the entry. This
        will hide the \"+\" button, so to show it again swipe from left to right on the entry
    </string>
    <string name="info_patterns">
        To add a new pattern just click on the \"+\" button in the bottom right corner.\n\n
        To show the edit and delete buttons of a pattern swipe from right to left on the entry. This
        will hide the \"+\" button, so to show it again swipe from left to right on the entry
    </string>
    <string name="rate_hint">
        It seems you have already got some name inspirations through my app ;) I would really
        appreciate your honest review on Google Play Store!
    </string>
    <string name="rate_hint_yes">
        Sure
    </string>
    <string name="rate_hint_no">
        No thanks
    </string>
</resources>
