<resources>
    <string-array name="sections">
        <item name="generator">Generator</item>
        <item name="names">Names</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">NMG</string>
    <string name="app_title" translatable="false">No Man\'s Generator</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="generator_empty_state">
        Swipe down to generate names. To generate new names again you have to eventually scroll to
        the top and then swipe down again.\n\n
        Check the right boxes to save  your favourites. \n\n
        The bottom bar can be used to set how many unique names should be generated on one swipe.
    </string>
    <string name="invalid_syllable_character">Syllables can only contain lowercase, unaccented, alphabetic characters</string>
    <string name="invalid_syllable_length">Syllables must be at least two characters long</string>
    <string name="invalid_syllable_vowel">Syllables must contain at least one vowel</string>
    <string name="invalid_pattern_no_braces">Must at least contain one pattern in curly braces {}</string>
    <string name="invalid_pattern_uneven_braces">Must have the same amount of opening { and closing } curly braces</string>
    <string name="invalid_pattern_start">Pattern must start with one of these characters: X/x (any), C/c (consonant), V/v (vowel)</string>
    <string name="invalid_pattern_length">Pattern length must be at least 1 and max. 9</string>
    <string name="invalid_pattern_range">Pattern range must be at least 1-1 and max.9-9</string>
    <string name="confirm_delete_syllable">Delete syllable?</string>
    <string name="confirm_delete_pattern">Delete pattern?</string>
    <string name="confirm_delete_name">Delete name?</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="title_save_pattern">Save pattern</string>
    <string name="title_save_syllable">Save syllable</string>
    <string name="title_save_name">Save name</string>
    <string name="ok" translatable="false">OK</string>
    <string name="title_info">Information</string>
    <string name="generator_info_no_syllables">You have no active syllables. Please activate or create some.</string>
    <string name="generator_info_no_patterns">You have no active patterns. Please activate or create some.</string>
    <string name="generator_info_no_consonant_syllables">You only have active patterns which require consonants but no active syllables that start with one.</string>
    <string name="generator_info_no_vowel_syllables">You only have active patterns which require vowels but no active syllables that start with one.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_used_libraries">Used Libraries</string>
    <string name="preference_about_app">About app</string>
    <string name="preference_patterns">Patterns</string>
    <string name="preference_syllables">Syllables</string>
    <string name="preference_about_app_used_libraries_summary">The android libraries I used to make this app so fancy.</string>
    <string name="preference_patterns_summary">Edit the patterns used for name generation.</string>
    <string name="preference_syllables_summary">Edit the syllables used for name generation.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_patterns">Patterns</string>
    <string name="title_activity_syllables">Syllables</string>
    <string name="generated_names_amount_selector">Generate %s</string>
    <string name="preference_feedback">Send feedback</string>
    <string name="preference_feedback_url">https://goo.gl/forms/BmL7Zh64fiJOjwNa2</string>
    <string name="preference_feedback_summary">Opens in your browser</string>
    <string name="preference_helper_summary">He translated the app into portuguese and has some cool projects too! Have a look: https://github.com/adrielcafe</string>
    <string name="preference_helper" translatable="false">Adriel Café</string>
    <string name="preference_patterns_tutorial">Tutorial</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tutorial">Tutorial</string>
    <string name="tutorial_main">
        To add a new name, syllable or pattern just click on the \"+\" button in the bottom right
        corner of the lists.\n\n

        To show the edit and delete buttons of a name, syllable or pattern simply swipe from right
        to left on the desired entry. This will hide the \"+\" button, so to show it again swipe
        from left to right on the entry.
    </string>
    <string name="tutorial_patterns">
        Patterns can contain fixed items but must always contain at least one syllable-part.\n\n
        A syllable-part has to start with a \"{\" and end with a \"}\".\n\n
        The first character of it must be either \"X\", \"C\" or \"V\". This determines if the
        first syllable should start with a consonant (C), a vowel (V) or if it can be random (X).
        Setting this character to lowercase or uppercase also sets the first character of the
        starting syllable to lowercase or uppercase.\n\n
        Then follows the amount of used syllables. Either set a fixed number between \"1\" and \"9\"
        or set a range between \"1-1\" to \"9-9\".\n\n
        Outside of these syllable parts, you can add anything you like and it will be added to the
        generated parts.\n\n\n\n

        To understand the previous text a bit better, I will explain what the patterns provided
        at installation will do.\n\n

        \"{X2-9}\" will generate names starting with an uppercase random syllable and these names
        will contain between 2 and 9 syllables.\n\n

        \"{V1} {C1}\'{c1-4}\" will generate names starting with one uppercase syllable that has a
        vowel as first character.\n
        Then follows a static blank space.\n
        Then one uppercase syllable that starts with a consonant will follow, directly followed by
        a static apostrophe.\n
        The last syllable-part will add a lowercase consonant syllable and will contain between 1
        and 4 syllables in total.
    </string>
    <string name="info_names">
        To add a new name just click on the \"+\" button in the bottom right corner.\n\n
        To show the edit and delete buttons of a name swipe from right to left on the entry. This
        will hide the \"+\" button, so to show it again swipe from left to right on the entry
    </string>
    <string name="info_syllables">
        To add a new syllable just click on the \"+\" button in the bottom right corner.\n\n
        To show the edit and delete buttons of a syllable swipe from right to left on the entry. This
        will hide the \"+\" button, so to show it again swipe from left to right on the entry
    </string>
    <string name="info_patterns">
        To add a new pattern just click on the \"+\" button in the bottom right corner.\n\n
        To show the edit and delete buttons of a pattern swipe from right to left on the entry. This
        will hide the \"+\" button, so to show it again swipe from left to right on the entry
    </string>
    <string name="rate_hint">
        It seems you have already got some name inspirations through my app ;) I would really
        appreciate your honest review on Google Play Store!
    </string>
    <string name="rate_hint_yes">
        Sure
    </string>
    <string name="rate_hint_no">
        No thanks
    </string>
</resources>
